technologyvista.com 2019-04-29

# Privacy Policy » Technology Vista

This Privacy Policy governs the way in which[  **www.TechnologyVista.com**](http://technologyvista.com/)[ ](http://honeybunni.com/ "honeybunni")collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the [www.TechnologyVista.com](http://technologyvista.com/) website. This Privacy Policy applies to the website, all products and services offered to users by [ **www.TechnologyVista.com**](http://technologyvista.com/ "honeybunni")

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you if and when you subscribe to our newsletter or News Information or you register in our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or mailing address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, may use cookies to serve ads on our site. If that is so, Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our sites & other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad & content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

******Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:**

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information & feedback we receive from you)
  * To send periodic emails
  * The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers complex drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser & capture & remember certain information

We use cookies to understand & save your preferences for future visits.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may moreover release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products & services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

[**www.TechnologyVista.com**](http://technologyvista.com/ "TechnologyVista") has the right to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of this website. We encourage users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modification and or any changes.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this privacy policy and terms of service. If you don’t agree to it, please don’t use this website. Your continued use of this website following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes/modifications.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
